

Tangerang, Banten 15510 🏫

087733875246 📞



harysaputra2703@gmail.com 💟



linkedin.com/in/harysaputra27 in

I am a Computer & Network Engineering graduate who has an interest in working in the IT field, especially Software Engineering. I am 21 years old this year, I am currently studying 4th semester undergraduate majoring in information systems at Pamulang University. Currently I have studied coding such as HTML, CSS, Databases and JavaScript independently.

Work Experience

JANUARY 2020 - MARCH 2020

Advertising (Intern)

PT GRANARY INDONESIA PROPERTY SERVICE. Jakarta

- Advertise property such as (Land, House, Apartment etc.).
- Create Listing Reports every month using Microsoft Excel.
- Monitor advertising developments.

JULI 2022 - MARET 2023

Waitress (Part Time)

Restoran Putra Arema. Tangerang

Education

2017 - 2020

SMK Labschool Tangerang Raya/ Computer network Engineering

Skills

- Microsoft Office.
- IT Networking.
- Advertising.
- Bahasa Indonesia.
- English basic

Hobby

- Coding
- Editing
- Fotografi